Welcome to the new feature introduction video of Marvelous Designer 2025.
In the current version, the grid four-sided painting algorithm has been optimized again.
First, to compare the top structure, we open the display frame function.
Go to the 3D window of the clothing rendering type, find the clothing rendering option, then open the display frame.
Select all panels, change the grid type to four-sided, optimize.
Then, the panel will be re-painted.
On the left is the four-sided painting costume of the 2024 version, and on the right is the 2025 version.
In the previous version, the structure of the pre-painting is not reasonable, but in the new version, it will be improved.
Although it is a relatively simple T-shirt,
the results of the four-sided painting in the two versions are also different.
The new version is more reasonable.
Let's add a more complex set of clothes.
The upper part of this skirt has folds, and the lower part has a lot of folds.
After the four-sided painting of this skirt, we will see that the structure after re-painting will try to maintain the original clothing shape.
Now, let's take a closer look at the details of the clothing.
After closing the display frame, we can check the clothing details better.
Let's check the effect after the grid transformation to four-sided painting.
Although the grid type and the fabric change, the overall detail is very small.
You can select to use one-piece four-sided painting, or manually re-paint.